The Switch is a crime film directed by Peter Maxwell.
A wristwatch-smuggling gang bring watches into the
country in a car's petrol tank.
Poor Zena Marshall knows too much, so the gangs abducts her.
Stalwart customs official Anthony Steel struggles manfully to rescue the girl.
Bill Craddock, played by Anthony Steel.
Caroline Markham, played by Zena Marshall.
John Curry, played by Conrad Phillips.
Inspector Tomlinson, played by Dermot Walsh.
Search Officer, played by Susan Shaw.
Janice Lampton, played by Dawn Beret.
The Switch is a 1963 British crime drama film directed by Peter Maxwell, and
starring Anthony Steel, Zena Marshall and Conrad Phillips.
It was written by Philip Ridgeway and Colin Fraser.
The film concerns a criminal gang that smuggles watches into the UK
by hiding them in the petrol tank of a woman's car.
It was Susan Shaw's last film.